(Stuart:)Oh, no. I don't want
to be an inconvenience.
(Stuart:)You've got all your
lady friends, and...
(Raj:)Actually, I'm single now.
What?!
(Stuart:)When did that happen?
(Raj:)It's okay. It's by choice.
(Raj:)Well, their choice,
and it's not okay.
(Stuart:)Oh. Sorry.
I didn't know.
(Raj:)Nobody does. I was embarrassed
so I didn't say anything.
(Bernadette:)Why wouldn't he tell us?
(Bernadette:)Are we bad friends?
(Howard:)He's in our hot tub
drinking our wine.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, he deserves
to be alone.
(Stuart:)So you're back out
on the dating scene now?
(Raj:)Yeah, yeah, a little.
(Stuart:)Oh, that must be fun.
How's that going?
(Raj:)I'm in a hot tub with you,
so pretty bad.
(Amy:)Maybe I should just give in
to his stupid bathroom schedule.
(Leonard:)No, don't do that.
- But you did!
- Exactly!
Learn from my mistakes!
No matter where
I am at 7:18 a.m.,
there better be
a toilet nearby.